

Senior Digital Product Designer | UX/UI, Web, Html & CSS, Mobile, Motion Graphics, Social Videos

ABOUT ME

66 I'm about researching client and user/market needs and creating dymnamic digital messaging and products using ctas, typeface, colour and layouts/wireframes that put user experience and user interface at the forefront.

UX/UI examples

Click to view

I'm a designer & I code

Click to view

Motion Graphics and Social Videos

Click to view

More on my webpage: https://edwinau.github.io/edwin-landing

WORK EXPERIENCE

Borden Ladner Gervais LLP

Senior Designer | Digital & Multimedia

Jan 2020 - Present www.blg.com



- Collaborate in the creation of company webpages for <u>BLG.com</u> and <u>BLG</u> <u>Beyond</u>; while applying best UX/UI practices, responsible for balancing speed, quality, and consistency of design with meeting firm objectives
- > Researching client and market needs and applying best site nav usage and webpage wireframes to determine optimized page patterns for best UX/UI results
- Responsible for providing final web assets including hero banners; inline animated graphics and infographs; and adjusting page responsiveness for Desktop and Mobile experiences by injecting custom HTML and CSS code
- > Providing social media assets including <u>digital Linkedin posts</u>, <u>social videos</u>, <u>gifs</u> and more

Blake, Cassels & Graydon LLP

Designer | Motion Graphics, Web, HTML





- > Heavy involvement in the launch of <u>blakes.com</u> from user research, site nav and working with wireframes; to providing final visual web assets including landing page banners, <u>homepage animated banners</u>, inline graphics and infographs, headshots, graphics for hover state flip tiles, and more
- > Working with <u>HTML and CSS</u> templates to facilitate client event eVites, working with CRM, B2B clients, spam filters and CASL compliance
- > Providing social media assets for <u>LinkedIn</u>, <u>Twitter</u>, Facebook, Instagram and Youtube
- > Providing assets for <u>digital event signage</u>, newsletters and internal communications as required

Disney Consumer Products

Consumer Product Designer 🔇 Nov 2013 - Mar 2016



- > Provided creative guidance in the design and development of Disney Branded Consumer Products sold across Walmart Canada, Target Canada, Canadian Tire, Toy R' Us, Dollarama, <u>Uniqlo</u> and more
- > Working with the team in leading 50+ licensees on 300+ products simultaneously and seasonally. Work days range from managing <u>online</u> <u>product design approvals</u>, to meeting with vendors communicating design goals and initiatives

<u>□ Dolce & Gabbana</u> (Milan, Italy)

Intern Sep 2012 - Oct 2013



> Having accumulated 10 years of fashion product development experience - I decided to take my skills abroad and resulted in a work placement with Dolce & Gabbana at their head quarters in Milan for 10 months; duties include input and preparation of their Fall 2013 and Spring 2014 collections. With direct exposure and experience to the European retail and merchandising landscape

SKILLS



Sketch















d A













EDUCATION

✓ Master Classes (IDF)

Storytelling Through Visual Design: with Ellen Lupton | Jan 2022

> Exploring visual design principles for desktop and mobile experiences through the exploration of storytelling and user journeys

General Assembly

Web Development Program

Mar 2017 - Jun 2017

- > Web Dev Immersive Full Stack Program with UX/UI experience
- > HTML5, CSS3, Sketch, Figma, JavaScript, Ruby, Rails, jQuery, AJAX, SQL, SASS

Toronto Metropolitan University

B.A.A. - Fashion Design Degree Sep 1998 - Apr 2002

- > Product Design, Graphic Design, Marketing, Trend Analysis
- > Fashion Communication with focus in R&D, working in agile environments

Birmingham City University (UK)

Merchandising and Design Jan 2001 - Aug 2001

- > Selected by Ryerson University to partake in the London, UK exchange program
- Thesis: Triple P bottom line and relation to green design